Guide to the Records,
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series XV: 1986 Addition
  - Minutes, 1954-1960 (Box 103)
  - Minutes, 1961-1969 (Box l04)
  - Minutes, 1970-1977 (Box 105)
  - Minutes, 1978 (Box 106)
- Series XVI: Printed Materials
  - The ABMAC Bulletin, 1939-1979, (5 Folders) (Box 107)
- Series XVII: Audio Visual, etc.
  - Subseries XVII.1: Photograph Albums
    - Cowdry's (Dr. and Mrs.) Trip to Taiwan (No. 1) (Box 109)
    - Miscellaneous (Nos. 2 & 3) (Box 109)
    - A Pictorial Exhibit of China's Health in War (No. 4) (Box 109)
  - Subseries XVII.2: Record Albums
    - Mme. Chiang Kai-Shek. Address to the House of Representatives of the USA, Washington DC, February 18, 1943 (No.1) 2 discs (Box 109)
    - Mme. Chiang Kai- Shek. Speech at Wellesley College, MA, 7 March 1943 (No. 2) 2 discs (Box 109)
    - Miscellaneous (No. 3) 12 discs (Box 109)
  - Subseries XVII.3: Phonograph Records
    - China On The March, 3/20/1941 (Box 536, Folder 1)
    - United China Relief, 4/27/1941 (Box 536, Folder 2)
    - United China Relief Program, 5/16/1941 [2 disks] (Box 536, Folder 3-1; 3-2)
    - United China Relief Program, 6/3/1941 (Box 536, Folder 4)
    - United China Relief Program, 6/6/1941 [2 disks] (Box 536, Folder 5-1; 5-2)
    - United China Relief Program, 7/1/1941 (Box 536, Folder 6)
    - United China Relief Program, 10/2/1941 (Box 536, Folder 7)
    - United China Relief Program, 4/1942 (Box 536, Folder 8)
    - March of Time: Chiang Kai-Shek (in Mandarin), 13 May 1942 [2 disks] (Box 535, Folder 9-1; 9-2)
    - Mme. Chiang Kai-Shek, 4 April 1943 (2 disks) (Box 535, Folder 10-1; 10-2)
    - Congressman Walter Judd, 3 February 1944 (Box 535, Folder 11)
    - United China Relief, Inc. "Let's Look At China", 1944 (Box 535, Folder 12)
    - "Join the News Reel", 10 February 1944 (Box 535, Folder 13)
    - "China News Reel", 10 February 1944 (Box 535, Folder 14)
    - "United China Relief", 13 March 1944 (Box 535, Folder 15)
    - "Army Day Parade", 8 April & 15 April 1944 (Box 535, Folder 16)
    - "China Relief Committee", 19 June 1947 (Box 535, Folder 17)
    - "United China War Relief", Undated (2 disks) (Box 535, Folder 18-1; 18-2)
    - "Why Help the Chinese?" (USC), Undated (Box 535, Folder 19)
    - "United China Relief: S. Speath", Undated (Box 535, Folder 20)
    - "United China Relief Program", Undated (Box 535, Folder 21)
    - Esteemed Grandparents (UCR) (Box 535, Folder 22)
  - Subseries XVII.4: Tapes
    - ABMAC Dinner in Honor of Liu Chieh, 7 December 1941 (Box 109, Folder 1)
    - ABMAC 20th anniversary, 1957 (Box 109, Folder 2)
    - ABMAC 25th Anniversary. Taipei, 29 October 1962 (Box 109, Folder 3)
    - ABMAC 30th Anniversary, 1967 (Box 109, Folder 4)
    - Dinner in Honor of C. K. Yen the Vice Pres. and Prime Minister of the Republic of China, 15 May 1967 (Box 109, Folder 5)
  - Subseries XVII.5: Motion Picture Films
    - ABMAC 25th Anniversary (2 reels) (Box 108)
  - Subseries XVII.6: Photographs, Posters, Drawings, and Scrapbook
    - Photographs (Box 12; 41e)
    - Posters:
      - Miscellaneous (1 Oversize Folder) (Box 12; 41e)
      - "United China Relief" (1 Oversize Folder) (Box 12; 41e)
      - "United Service to China (1 Oversize Folder) (Box 12; 41e)
    - Drawings - Water Color (Box 12; 41e)
    - Scrapbook 1 Volume (Box 109)
    - Painting of a bird, with calligraphy (Box 5)
    - Painting depicting demons and men, possibly royal (Box 6)